// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: " 8433.733 ÷ 54.102 ÷ 5.55 = ?",
    answer: "28",
    options: [
      "27",
      "28",
      "25",
      "20"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The product of two consecutive odd numbers is 4623. Which is the smaller of the two numbers?",
    answer: " 67",
    options: [
      "45",
      "56",
      "67",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "If the numerator of a fraction is increased by 200% and denominator is increased by 400%, the resultant fraction is 12/18. What was the original fraction?",
    answer: "10/9",
    options: [
      "10/9",
      "9/10",
      "10/19",
      "13/9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "45 men can do a piece of work in 20 days. How many men would be required to do the same work in 30 days ?",
    answer: "30",
    options: [
      "32",
      " 35",
      "30",
      "29"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which number should replace both the question marks in the following equation ? / 125 = 72 / ?",
    answer: "60",
    options: [
      "30",
      " 60",
      "67",
      "29"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Rs. 7,50,000 are invested in Rs. 100 shares which are quoted at Rs.1200. Find the income if 25 % dividend is declared on the shares.",
    answer: "15625",
    options: [
      "15225",
      " 15625",
      "16000",
      "12345"
    ]
  }
,

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Find the value added tax paid by shopkeeper if he buys a Sofa set for $10000 and pays 7% tax and sells the Sofa set for $ 13,000 and charges 9% tax.",
    answer: "470",
    options: [
      "789",
      " 470",
      "308",
      "290"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " 512, 100, 216, 64 , __ , 36, 8, 16. ",
    answer: "64",
    options: [
      "64",
      " 26",
      "48",
      "190"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Find the difference between the C.I. and the S.I. on Rs. 4000 @8% p.a. in 2 years",
    answer: "Rs. 25.60",
    options: [
      "Rs. 35.60",
      " Rs. 49.60",
      "Rs. 45.60",
      "Rs. 25.60"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " What will be the Rate of Interest? If Salman has a recurring deposit account in a bank. He deposits Rs. 2500/month for 2 years. If he gets Rs. 66250 at the time of maturity. .",
    answer: "10%",
    options: [
      "12%",
      " 10%",
      "70%",
      "34%"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: " In a bag there are 2 Yellow, 3 Violet, 6 Black and 4 Blue balls. If two balls are picked at random, what is the probability that either both are yellow or both are violet ?",
    answer: "None of these",
    options: [
      "60/91",
      " 69/71",
      "69/91",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: " 1369 1521 1681 1849 ?",
    answer: "2025",
    options: [
      "2015",
      " 2025",
      "2035",
      "2028"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "39% of 485 – 22% of 516 = ? – 1008 . ",
    answer: "1083.63",
    options: [
      "1083.66",
      " 281.63",
      "281.78",
      "1083.63"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question: " What will be the third proportional to 6 and 12 ?",
    answer: "24",
    options: [
      "22",
      " 10",
      "None of these",
      "24"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Harish purchased a Jewellery marked at 536500 at a discount of 8%. If the VAT is charged at the rate of 10%, find the amount paid by the jewellery ?",
    answer: "542938",
    options: [
      "429200",
      "542938",
      " 429200",
      "None of these"
    ]
  }
    
];